Personal
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Personal
2.1.2.1.4
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1343
- Personal, 2.1.2.1.4
  - Lowell Thomas in Arab headdress, 1918; 12; 4-1; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - T. E. Lawrence and Lowell Thomas squatting in front of tent, Arabia, 1918; 13; 4-2; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - T. E. Lawrence and Lowell Thomas squatting in front of tent, Arabia, 1918; 14; 4-2; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas and T.E. Lawrence standing in front of tent, Arabia, 1918; 15; 4-3; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas and T.E. Lawrence standing in front of tent, Arabia, 1918; 16; 4-3; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - T. E. Lawrence and Lowell Thomas squatting in London in Arab clothes, circa 1919; 17; 4-4; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - T. E. Lawrence and Lowell Thomas squatting in London in Arab clothes, circa 1919; 18; 4-4; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas on Arab horse [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: An Arab thoroughbred], 1918; 19; 4-12; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas on Arab horse [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: An Arab thoroughbred], 1918; 20; 4-12; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas on Emir Feisal’s horse, 1918; 21; 4-13; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Profile view of Lowell Thomas and General Edmund Allenby, close-up [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Allenby and author], 1918; 22; 4-16; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - General Edmund Allenby[?] and others on hill top, 1918; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - General Edmund Allenby and his staff, 1918; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - General Edmund Allenby leaving a Bethlehem church, 1917 15 Dec; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas with movie camera in airplane before taking off for a flight from Egypt to Jerusalem [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Lowell Thomas in an open cockpit Breguet about to take off with Major A. J. Evans to follow the route of the Israelites across the Sinai Desert], 1918; 26; 4-17; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas with mayor of Gaza having a quiet smoke, the mayor’s nephews at right, 1918; 27; 4-18; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas with mayor of Gaza having a quiet smoke, the mayor’s nephews at right, 1918; 28; 4-18; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas in armored car in the valley of the Dead Sea, 1000 feet below sea level, 1918; 29; 4-22; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas in armored car in the valley of the Dead Sea, 1000 feet below sea level, 1918; 30; 4-22; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - General Giuseppe “Peppino” Garibaldi and dog, Lowell Thomas not looking at camera, 1918; 31; 4-31; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Harry Chase in Arab clothes, three quarter view, London, circa 1919; 32; 4-42; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas in pith helmet, circa 1919; 33; 4-47; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas’s passport, Germany, 1919 January 9; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas’s passport, Germany, 1918 December 17; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas’s passport, Switzerland, 1918 December 6; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas’s passport, Sudan, 1918; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas standing by fountain, distant view, circa 1918-1921; 38; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  Box 1344
- Personal, 2.1.2.1.4
  - Airplane on ground with pilot in front cockpit, Harry Chase stands in back seat while operating movie camera, 1918; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1344)
  - Lowell Thomas and seaman examining a torpedo[?] on board the deck of a ship, 1918; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1344)
  - Lowell Thomas filming with movie camera on board a ship, 1918; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1344)
  - Lowell Thomas, soldiers and woman at unidentified estate, 1918; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1344)
  - Lowell Thomas stands before the Chicago Daily News building with three other men, circa 1917 - early 1920s; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1344)
  - Cartoon impression of Lowell Thomas at the Albert Hall where he is continuing his famous lecture on Allenby in Palestine by Ernest Forbes, circa 1919; 6; 3x4 b&w (Box 1344)
  - Cartoon impression of Lowell Thomas, circa 1919; 7; 3x4 b&w (Box 1344)